<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DFS Consulting]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DFS Consulting]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 05:59:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>How a 20 Year Old Started A Consulting Business From His Parents Garage In New Zealand, Moved To Manhattan And Made Over $100,000 In Just Six Months! Last year I was decided To Start Playing DFS on Fanduel and Draftkings. For a couple months i was striking out (literally) I would research the way I felt would give me an edge and I was losing much more than I was making. Then, one day I crafted a Simple 3- Step Research guideline For Myself to Maximize my daily lineup's potential and it caught fire! 1 win, 2 wins, 3 wins and then it was rocking and I was winning so much I had to share this. From $25, Over the next 2 months I made $7000. The next month - $12,000. The next $22,625. The next - $32,000 and now this month (July) I have already made $45,000 and we're only a couple days in. I traded in my old run down car for my dream car, BRAND NEW . Friends and People started noticing my results and talking about my story and before long I had people asking me to teach them how to start playing DFS using my 3- Step Research and how to make wild amounts of money . At first I said "No" because I honestly didn't believe that anybody else could apply what I was doing. I thought I was unique and that nobody else would be able to make it work. But this one guy Rodrigo just wouldn't give up and he was consistent as hell! He would email me 2-3 times per day telling me he wanted to learn my methods and that he was even willing to pay me. After a few months of non-stop messages I gave in and decided to try teaching my methods to Stanley. I didn't even think it would work for him but he begged me to do it... We jumped on Skype calls twice per week and I taught him my process from start to finish. Within three weeks I couldn't believe it... Stanley won his first $10,000. I almost fell off my chair! Stanley went from knowing NOTHING about DFS or sports in general and within three weeks he deposited his first amount for $10,000. I wondered if this could be replicated again so I accepted 2 more people and showed them how to do it and then BAM - they started winning too! Then I started working with more people, the groups grew from 10 to 20 to 30 and I kept teaching them my same methods and they kept getting results. Fast Forward to this current day and I now have 41 partners making tens of thousands of dollar incomes from my advice and trainings. It's honestly hard to believe how this happened so fast.How have I created extreme liquid wealth for myself and my clients in such a short time? Well it all comes down to relentless focus on 3 Key things... We live in an ADD world where there is too much information and too many distractions. While others have tried to do it all - I have tried to do less. In the modern world it's more about what your ignore rather than what you do. While others burn themselves out trying to do 52 different things I focus on 3. Want to know what these 3 key things are? I spent the past week putting together a free training for you showing you *exactly* how I got started and grew my consulting business into the millions. I literally pull back the curtain and reveal it all including the "3 Key Things" that have been the foundation of my success and my students success.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedhow-a-20-year-old-started-a-consulting-business-from-his-par/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">56f3900b-bc42-42e5-a82b-efa79119c8ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 05:59:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>